[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 27, "question": "How are they going to find closure given they see such injustice here?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "they", "going", "to", "find", "closure", "given", "they", "see", "such", "injustice", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", "VBN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 28, "answer": "I wouldn't say they are angry.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "n't", "say", "they", "are", "angry", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 53, "question": "Do you think the prosecution dropped the ball in that regard and they should have had more people talking about the human being that Trayvon Martin was?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "the", "prosecution", "dropped", "the", "ball", "in", "that", "regard", "and", "they", "should", "have", "had", "more", "people", "talking", "about", "the", "human", "being", "that", "Trayvon", "Martin", "was", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "RBR", "NNS", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 54, "answer": "No, I won't criticize the prosecution.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "wo", "n't", "criticize", "the", "prosecution", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Trayvon Martin"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Boston"]}, "docId": "130718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 106, "question": "What was your view of it?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "your", "view", "of", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 107, "answer": "I was not nearly as upset as many of the people in Boston are.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "not", "nearly", "as", "upset", "as", "many", "of", "the", "people", "in", "Boston", "are", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jesse Jackson", "Al Sharpton"]}, "docId": "130718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "CC", "WP", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "CC", "NNS", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 122, "question": "What is your view about the verdict?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "view", "about", "the", "verdict", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 123, "answer": "Well, first, this case was not about race at all and what happened, you have the race hustlers and poverty pimps like Jesse Jackson and Al Sharpton, and others who turned it into a race issue in order to gain power and wealth.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "first", ",", "this", "case", "was", "not", "about", "race", "at", "all", "and", "what", "happened", ",", "you", "have", "the", "race", "hustlers", "and", "poverty", "pimps", "like", "Jesse", "Jackson", "and", "Al", "Sharpton", ",", "and", "others", "who", "turned", "it", "into", "a", "race", "issue", "in", "order", "to", "gain", "power", "and", "wealth", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George Zimmerman"]}, "docId": "130718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "RP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 135, "question": "You really think George Zimmerman would have looked at a young white man in a hoodie and thought the same thing, that this guy is potential trouble?", "question_tokens": ["You", "really", "think", "George", "Zimmerman", "would", "have", "looked", "at", "a", "young", "white", "man", "in", "a", "hoodie", "and", "thought", "the", "same", "thing", ",", "that", "this", "guy", "is", "potential", "trouble", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 136, "answer": "Well, George Zimmerman would have done whatever it took to protect himself.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "George", "Zimmerman", "would", "have", "done", "whatever", "it", "took", "to", "protect", "himself", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George Zimmerman"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "EX", "VBD", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ":", "VBG", ":", "VBG", "IN", "TO", "DT", "NN", ",", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 161, "question": "Everyone who smokes pot in America is a thug, are they?", "question_tokens": ["Everyone", "who", "smokes", "pot", "in", "America", "is", "a", "thug", ",", "are", "they", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 162, "answer": "Well, you know, there were pictures on his Facebook page of Trayvon Martin carrying -- having -- holding on to a gun, pot in front of him.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "there", "were", "pictures", "on", "his", "Facebook", "page", "of", "Trayvon", "Martin", "carrying", "--", "having", "--", "holding", "on", "to", "a", "gun", ",", "pot", "in", "front", "of", "him", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNP", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "RB", "IN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 168, "question": "I mean, you're saying everyone in America that has ever taken cannabis or ever been pictured with a gun is a thug, is that your -- is that your conclusion?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "you", "'re", "saying", "everyone", "in", "America", "that", "has", "ever", "taken", "cannabis", "or", "ever", "been", "pictured", "with", "a", "gun", "is", "a", "thug", ",", "is", "that", "your", "--", "is", "that", "your", "conclusion", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", ":", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 169, "answer": "Before they took his information off of his Facebook page, it was out there for everybody to see.", "answer_tokens": ["Before", "they", "took", "his", "information", "off", "of", "his", "Facebook", "page", ",", "it", "was", "out", "there", "for", "everybody", "to", "see", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 172, "question": "Where was the evidence that he was a dangerous thug?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "was", "the", "evidence", "that", "he", "was", "a", "dangerous", "thug", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 173, "answer": "He would -- he had been in trouble before.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "would", "--", "he", "had", "been", "in", "trouble", "before", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Trayvon Martin"]}, "docId": "130718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 185, "question": "What do you think about all this?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "about", "all", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 186, "answer": "You know, I think that Trayvon Martin at the end of the day was a 16-year-old kid.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "think", "that", "Trayvon", "Martin", "at", "the", "end", "of", "the", "day", "was", "a", "16-year-old", "kid", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "JJS", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "DT", "DT", "NNP", "POS", "VBD", "VBN", "CC", "DT", "DT", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "RP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 219, "question": "What would you like, if anything, for President Obama to do?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "you", "like", ",", "if", "anything", ",", "for", "President", "Obama", "to", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 220, "answer": "At least go through it with a fine-tooth comb and just make sure all the T's were crossed and all the I's were dotted because this is setting a terrible message -- it's sending out a terrible message to young teenagers.", "answer_tokens": ["At", "least", "go", "through", "it", "with", "a", "fine-tooth", "comb", "and", "just", "make", "sure", "all", "the", "T", "'s", "were", "crossed", "and", "all", "the", "I", "'s", "were", "dotted", "because", "this", "is", "setting", "a", "terrible", "message", "--", "it", "'s", "sending", "out", "a", "terrible", "message", "to", "young", "teenagers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Reverend Peterson"]}, "docId": "130718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", ":", "RB", "TO", ":", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 230, "question": "What do you say to that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "say", "to", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 231, "answer": "Well, I certainly disagree with -- respectfully to -- with Reverend Peterson.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "certainly", "disagree", "with", "--", "respectfully", "to", "--", "with", "Reverend", "Peterson", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Reverend Peterson"]}, "docId": "130718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBZ", ":", "JJ", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 244, "question": "You guys -- you guys are hypocrites because if you truly cared about black Americans, why aren't you upset about the 500 homicides that took place in Chicago last year?", "question_tokens": ["You", "guys", "--", "you", "guys", "are", "hypocrites", "because", "if", "you", "truly", "cared", "about", "black", "Americans", ",", "why", "are", "n't", "you", "upset", "about", "the", "500", "homicides", "that", "took", "place", "in", "Chicago", "last", "year", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "WDT", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 245, "answer": "You see, I think this is -- Reverend Peterson.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "see", ",", "I", "think", "this", "is", "--", "Reverend", "Peterson", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Chicago"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 277, "question": "What am I not telling the truth about?", "question_tokens": ["What", "am", "I", "not", "telling", "the", "truth", "about", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 278, "answer": "You call us hypocrites.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "call", "us", "hypocrites", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 288, "question": "Reverend Peterson, will you -- will you let Raymond Santana speak?", "question_tokens": ["Reverend", "Peterson", ",", "will", "you", "--", "will", "you", "let", "Raymond", "Santana", "speak", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "NNP", ",", "MD", "PRP", ":", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 289, "answer": "Yes, let me speak.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "let", "me", "speak", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Peterson", "Raymond Santana"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "VBZ", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 316, "question": "ETERSON: Why don't you became aware on the black on black crime?", "question_tokens": ["ETERSON", ":", "Why", "do", "n't", "you", "became", "aware", "on", "the", "black", "on", "black", "crime", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "WRB", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 317, "answer": "Crime is crime regardless.", "answer_tokens": ["Crime", "is", "crime", "regardless", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George Zimmerman", "Trayvon Martin"]}, "docId": "130718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "CC", "NN", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "RB", "TO", ",", "CC", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "VBN", "RP", "RB", "IN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "CC", "NN", ",", "IN", "RB", ",", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "CD", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 335, "question": "Only George Zimmerman had the right to defend himself with a gun, right?", "question_tokens": ["Only", "George", "Zimmerman", "had", "the", "right", "to", "defend", "himself", "with", "a", "gun", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 336, "answer": "Trayvon -- he had a right to defend himself but nothing came out during the trial that George Zimmerman stalked Trayvon Martin, nor did he follow him after he was told not to, and that lie is being put out there in order to divide and conquer, as well, by keeping blacks and whites angry at one another.", "answer_tokens": ["Trayvon", "--", "he", "had", "a", "right", "to", "defend", "himself", "but", "nothing", "came", "out", "during", "the", "trial", "that", "George", "Zimmerman", "stalked", "Trayvon", "Martin", ",", "nor", "did", "he", "follow", "him", "after", "he", "was", "told", "not", "to", ",", "and", "that", "lie", "is", "being", "put", "out", "there", "in", "order", "to", "divide", "and", "conquer", ",", "as", "well", ",", "by", "keeping", "blacks", "and", "whites", "angry", "at", "one", "another", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George Zimmerman"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", ",", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 357, "question": "How do you see a way through this?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "see", "a", "way", "through", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 358, "answer": "But, Piers, why do his family --", "answer_tokens": ["But", ",", "Piers", ",", "why", "do", "his", "family", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 376, "question": "Where did you get this man from?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "did", "you", "get", "this", "man", "from", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 377, "answer": "I said the same thing.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "said", "the", "same", "thing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 380, "question": "Sir, can you be respectful?", "question_tokens": ["Sir", ",", "can", "you", "be", "respectful", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 381, "answer": "Trying to turn a thug into a hero.", "answer_tokens": ["Trying", "to", "turn", "a", "thug", "into", "a", "hero", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NN", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 417, "question": "Do you feel that race inevitably, as it did in the trial involving O.J. Simpson, that race was at the center of this trial?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "feel", "that", "race", "inevitably", ",", "as", "it", "did", "in", "the", "trial", "involving", "O.J.", "Simpson", ",", "that", "race", "was", "at", "the", "center", "of", "this", "trial", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NN", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 418, "answer": "No, I don't think that race was the center.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "that", "race", "was", "the", "center", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["O.J. Simpson"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBG", "IN", "WP", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 430, "question": "But as -- the point I was going to make, really, was that in your trial, for example, involving the death of your brother and others, having such a predominantly black jury, do you feel that the race element of that, of the jury selection led them to acquit somebody who many people believe should have been convicted because some people are saying in the Zimmerman trial that had you had more African-Americans on the jury than they would have related better perhaps to Trayvon Martin, to his background, to the star witness Rachel Jeantel, and you could perhaps have had a different verdict?", "question_tokens": ["But", "as", "--", "the", "point", "I", "was", "going", "to", "make", ",", "really", ",", "was", "that", "in", "your", "trial", ",", "for", "example", ",", "involving", "the", "death", "of", "your", "brother", "and", "others", ",", "having", "such", "a", "predominantly", "black", "jury", ",", "do", "you", "feel", "that", "the", "race", "element", "of", "that", ",", "of", "the", "jury", "selection", "led", "them", "to", "acquit", "somebody", "who", "many", "people", "believe", "should", "have", "been", "convicted", "because", "some", "people", "are", "saying", "in", "the", "Zimmerman", "trial", "that", "had", "you", "had", "more", "African-Americans", "on", "the", "jury", "than", "they", "would", "have", "related", "better", "perhaps", "to", "Trayvon", "Martin", ",", "to", "his", "background", ",", "to", "the", "star", "witness", "Rachel", "Jeantel", ",", "and", "you", "could", "perhaps", "have", "had", "a", "different", "verdict", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", ":", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", ",", "RB", ",", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "NNS", ",", "VBG", "JJ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "NN", "WP", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "WDT", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "JJR", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "RBR", "RB", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 431, "answer": "Well, I guess that's the case in every trial, depending on who the jurors are.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "guess", "that", "'s", "the", "case", "in", "every", "trial", ",", "depending", "on", "who", "the", "jurors", "are", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Zimmerman", "Trayvon Martin", "Rachel Jeantel"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 440, "question": "Do you ever get any sense of closure?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "ever", "get", "any", "sense", "of", "closure", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 441, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 458, "question": "And would you recommend that course of action to people who feel a sense of injustice?", "question_tokens": ["And", "would", "you", "recommend", "that", "course", "of", "action", "to", "people", "who", "feel", "a", "sense", "of", "injustice", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "TO", "NNS", "WP", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 459, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 467, "question": "Has it brought you any satisfaction, perhaps a sense of karma that O.J. Simpson is currently incarcerated and maybe for a very long time for another offense?", "question_tokens": ["Has", "it", "brought", "you", "any", "satisfaction", ",", "perhaps", "a", "sense", "of", "karma", "that", "O.J.", "Simpson", "is", "currently", "incarcerated", "and", "maybe", "for", "a", "very", "long", "time", "for", "another", "offense", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "CC", "RB", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 468, "answer": "I love it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "love", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["O.J. Simpson"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 495, "question": "What is your actual view about self-defense and Stand Your Ground and so on?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "actual", "view", "about", "self-defense", "and", "Stand", "Your", "Ground", "and", "so", "on", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "RB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 496, "answer": "Well, I mean, I guess if I was ever in that situation, I'd be very happy for the self-defense law.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "I", "guess", "if", "I", "was", "ever", "in", "that", "situation", ",", "I", "'d", "be", "very", "happy", "for", "the", "self-defense", "law", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Stand Your Ground"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBG", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "EX", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "EX", "."], "qSentId": 541, "question": "What is your memory of what happened?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "memory", "of", "what", "happened", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "WP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 542, "answer": "I remember just, you know, us having fun and it was a little uncomfortable because there was so many people there.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "remember", "just", ",", "you", "know", ",", "us", "having", "fun", "and", "it", "was", "a", "little", "uncomfortable", "because", "there", "was", "so", "many", "people", "there", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "RB", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 550, "question": "And second, in that moment, what made you react the way that you did?", "question_tokens": ["And", "second", ",", "in", "that", "moment", ",", "what", "made", "you", "react", "the", "way", "that", "you", "did", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "JJ", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 551, "answer": "Before actually my parents kind of taught me to be aware of my surroundings.", "answer_tokens": ["Before", "actually", "my", "parents", "kind", "of", "taught", "me", "to", "be", "aware", "of", "my", "surroundings", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 563, "question": "But are you OK physically yourself now?", "question_tokens": ["But", "are", "you", "OK", "physically", "yourself", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "NNP", "RB", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 564, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 572, "question": "Was that part of your thinking when you said yes to his marriage proposal?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "that", "part", "of", "your", "thinking", "when", "you", "said", "yes", "to", "his", "marriage", "proposal", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "NNS", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 573, "answer": "Oh, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Eugene"]}, "docId": "130718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "NNP", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 578, "question": "Why did you choose, Kristin, the anniversary to get married?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "did", "you", "choose", ",", "Kristin", ",", "the", "anniversary", "to", "get", "married", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", ",", "NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 579, "answer": "Actually, Eugene chose it, not me so --", "answer_tokens": ["Actually", ",", "Eugene", "chose", "it", ",", "not", "me", "so", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kristin"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 610, "question": "Did he take a lot of weed?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "he", "take", "a", "lot", "of", "weed", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 611, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 612, "question": "How much would you say?", "question_tokens": ["How", "much", "would", "you", "say", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 613, "answer": "Like twice a week.", "answer_tokens": ["Like", "twice", "a", "week", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 614, "question": "Twice a week?", "question_tokens": ["Twice", "a", "week", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 615, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 616, "question": "Is that normal for teenagers in your community?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "normal", "for", "teenagers", "in", "your", "community", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 617, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]